module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: '“It\'s either haunted or a piece of shit."', 
      a: 'Jane Degen',
      b: 'Caitlin Checkett',
      c: 'Tomi Keah',
      d: 'Molly Hoke',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: '"I can send you a pic of the dead beaver, if you want…"', 
      a: 'Autumn Tran',
      b: 'Jessica Richardson',
      c: 'Catherine Crim',
      d: 'Beth Damiano',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: '"We go in and touch all teams."', 
      a: 'Brian Cahak',
      b: 'Jonathan Coffman',
      c: 'Brandon Jacobs',
      d: 'David Neff',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: '"Don\'t pee in my forest."', 
      a: 'Colby Riggle',
      b: 'Jenni Bruckman',
      c: 'Mark Couvillion',
      d: 'Kellee Jamison',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: '"My need for validation is infinite. IT\'S EXHAUSTING."', 
      a: 'Cara Daniels',
      b: 'Devon Moubry',
      c: 'BDF',
      d: 'Dan Cardamone',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: '"You\'ve got a face for lickin!"', 
      a: 'Lauren Walker',
      b: 'Matt Policastro',
      c: 'Jeremy Lindsley',
      d: 'Lynn Hunt',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: '"You can\'t eat crab without both butt cheeks planted."', 
      a: 'Josh Jalaliani',
      b: 'Crystal Pang',
      c: 'Kendra Bones',
      d: 'Mark Perica',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: '"Tongue so good"', 
      a: 'Juan Reyes',
      b: 'Marcus Luna',
      c: 'RA',
      d: 'Elliott Wenstrup',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: '"Do you guys do any work here? Just seems like everybody is having fun."', 
      a: 'flu shot lady',
      b: 'knife guy',
      c: 'everyone\'s chiropractor',
      d: 'dentist at ATX dental',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: '"Maybe I need to start being more dangerous"', 
      a: 'Haley McMichael',
      b: 'Sean Gardner',
      c: 'Archana Jayakumar',
      d: 'Joelle Baldacci',
      answer: 'a'
    }
  ]
};
